(Amy:)It was a lot hotter
than it sounds.
(Alfred:)You're a patient
young lady.
Hey, hey!
She's mine! Take a cold shower,
grandpa!
(Howard:)Why wouldn't that colonel say
what the meeting's about?
(Howard:)It has to be bad news.
(Raj:)Calm down, okay?
Try not to think about it.
(Howard:)That's really stupid advice.
(Raj:)You know that hurts
my feelings.
(Howard:)Calm down, try not
to think about it.
(Sheldon:)Okay.
(Howard:)Why do I bother
talking to you?
(Raj:)Oh, come on. What's the worst
that could come of this meeting?
(Howard:)I don't know. They take
the invention away,
(Howard:)and I get nothing?
(Raj:)Okay, that's not so bad.
(Raj:)You know what happened
to the scientists
(Raj:)that worked
on the Manhattan Project?
(Raj:)The government forced them
to move to the desert.
(Raj:)They had to live in secret,
and when Oppenheimer objected
(Raj:)to what they made him do,
(Raj:)they destroyed his reputation.
(Howard:)What's the point of that story?
(Raj:)I just read a book
about Oppenheimer,